The scene that happened yesterday morning was that my
TVS scooter which is an end
former writer and officer news friend if you don't
put it then they will ask all these
old coins are still there my
big feet are broken ah a a
book
that I should buy for them tomorrow otherwise now I will
call Raees down and give him a lot
on WhatsApp I will
loot you if you are doing a
comedy show in Alipur then
you will also order it I could have left the car there
you get it ordered
now tell me support me it will come
here
Dharam
1616 now whatever it is, let
me tell you that I don't have anything in the party that if it is
Diwali you will order it Mukesh will not stand then
where will you go otherwise
[music] I also have a
good amount so give it here
that Amar Bhaiya will call tomorrow after 5 minutes to someone
else
thank you
photocopy of RC insurance driving
license is
that Ashok should sing that you will have to get it
for me brother I will not come to the office it is of the company
not that
he will do it for the biggest show me
how much test match he is doing  1628 123 need
sugar approximately two
I Suraj you have seen what all
remedies are right if your insurance
claim
that her husband will go
yes tell me what you think we will decide then I have
some videos on Hindi subject
friends
how are you
[music]
that garlic no no no comparison
updated oh
we got looted get looted
Reliance bangles right now and someone else this one
which we have kept semolina if ah
what is written here I don't understand get
looted
you must have faith here
brother what should be done behind will never happen the
whole monastery that girl will get scared
old man closed
Jhalawar Rajasthan
nothing friend it is fake it has come
why won't you do it www
which is a big dushmani and below and above there are
scratches also simple cigarette
hey brother when he ever hit from here then I will send it by
cutting it with normal friend then this is the
way
I said
Thakur Manoj Mishra song when you leave your house
then here a guy from UP saw people getting the
local closed and getting
online
looted  The establishment net is running, did
they rob it, did they make some mistake,
now I do half the
green in biochemistry,
this video was done on YouTube and Facebook,
both of their deputy chief Deepak Chaurasia Dr. The
British Bar has got this video, it will
help you, you need documentation, when
you have to click on insurance, Aishwarya got
feedback,
if you get insurance of TVS tender or Reliance, then
you will know what
percentage you have to pay, bumper-to-bumper,
I got it done because of that,
and get it done mostly from Bajaj Allianz,
so till now I was
driving my car for my survival, that was for my kidneys, so
I paid only one fee, bumper-to-bumper,
he had the right vitamins, the cancer was cured,
you can check the quality of Khao and A Mai,
videos coming soon and like
I can open the door of the car,
I can check it as per the outside, so I
hope you liked this video, now
whatever happens tomorrow, I will keep sharing it with you, if you
like it, please like, share and
subscribe to the channel.  See you
in the next video, done by take care